She's tougher than she looks.
She is training
to be a Jedi after all.
A rookie who drops
her own lightsaber. but still. A Jedi.
Well. she was carrying
more than one.
What do you think her next move will be?
Jedi love to make a show
of helping the innocent.
I doubt she'll fight back.
She'll just keep running.
She can run all she wants.
but she won't escape.
The Jedi are fools.
Always making the same mistakes.
My Lord. repairs
on the kyber cannon have been completed.
I assume all it needs now
is a giant kyber crystal.
I beg you. please stay back.
Eesha?
Eesha's been taken hostage?
No...
Four-Nines. have you found
Nawaam's destination yet?
Hy Izlan?
He must be after
the Sacred Crystal in the Aerial Temple.
Make sure that Ethan knows about this.
What is it?
Huh?
Look. Just in from Four-Nines.
This can't be right!
You're the ones. aren't you?
Who took my father...
Are you going to kill me now?
That's not for us to decide.
Hey. hey. hey. hey!
That'd be a waste. don't you think?
They still might be of some use to us.
It'll make more sense to bring
at least one of them along.
Don't you dare!
Why bother?
It's too much work for too little payoff.
Fine.
But you've gotta admit.
Credits are still credits. though.
Am I right?
Make yourself scarce
before he changes his mind.
Kara!
Are you taking me to Nawaam?
Not yet. Got a little detour.
We're headed to recapture Zhima.
Father?
Word is. he went on a bit
of a rampage on one of Nawaam's outposts.
Wiped the whole place out by himself.
Jedi... Sith... There's no difference.
They both leave behind
the same trail of destruction.
No. you're wrong!
The Jedi fight in the name of justice.
Let me ask you this.
How many people have you killed
for the sake of justice?
Power is power.
You're strong. or you're weak.
That's all there is to it.
It's got nothing to do
with justice or evil.
So that's it then?
You think power is all that matters?
Take a good look
at yourself right now.
What good has your righteousness done you?
Give it a rest.
Quit obsessing
about archaic Jedi teachings.
You know. if you did.
you might actually be a match for us.
Are you planning on fighting me?
There's nothing I enjoy more
than fighting a strong enemy.
That's why I chose
this line of work. after all.
And that is also why you turned out
to be such a disappointment.
What does he mean by that?
I've done my best
to follow all the Jedi teachings.
But I don't know
what I'm doing anymore.
What's wrong. Kara?
Juro!
I gave in to the dark side.
I failed you.
Kara. why would you think
something like that?
Because when it mattered.
I couldn't control my feelings.
And then my lightsaber. it turned red.
All those lightsabers your father forged.
they have the ability to reflect
the wielder's thoughts and emotions.
For example.
the color red symbolizes
the feelings of rage. hatred and fear.
Being a Jedi doesn't mean
not having these feelings.
As long as you
do not let them control you.
then you will not succumb
to the dark side.
But I... I killed all of those people...
And I'm afraid of it happening again.
I can't fight anymore.
I just can't risk it.
So. when those in need
come seeking your help.
will you refuse to assist them?
But what am I supposed to do?
Unfortunately. that is a question
I do not have the answer to.
If even you don't know what to do.
then how am I supposed to?
Trust in the Force.
And if you do. you will be naturally
guided to the answer you seek.
The Force flows through
every single living thing.
So long as we follow
wherever it guides us.
we will always find our true path.
Kara. I hope that whatever answer
that you do find
will lead you to a new solution
that is different
from our old way of life.
Juro!
Juro...
Have you found anything?
We need to know where he's going.
Understood?
He caused
all of this destruction.
and yet. didn't take a single life.
Why go to the trouble?
Must be on some mercy kick.
- Idiot.
- Yup.
Hurry up and get to the control room
to look for clues.
Be safe. Father.
Find anything?
There are signs
of data being accessed.
Ah. He's going after Nawaam.
By himself?
Typical Jedi.
What do we do now?
Well. at this rate.
he's going to get to Nawaam
before we have a chance to intercept him.
If he does.
then we won't be able to take him in.
which means we won't get paid.
All this will have been for nothing.
We can't have that. now. can we?
We have no choice but to use the girl
to lure Zhima out.
Normally. I'd complain
that we're using the same trick twice.
but for once. I agree with you.
Their dirty little tricks...
They think they can use me
so they can set a trap for my father.
Think again!
Hmm?
What?
I won't let you touch my father!
I'm afraid Gennoh has his heart set
on having a rematch with him.
I don't care!
You were supposed to be bait.
but that's no longer an option.
Time to die.
Smoke?
No. wait. Mist.
How good a fighter are you?
Does the Force actually guide you?
I'd expect
nothing less from a Jedi.
But how long
will you be able to keep evading?
Eht. how do you expect me
to back you up?
Just shut up and watch.
That lightsaber makes you look
just like a Sith.
Shut up!
But then again. so does the way
you let your emotions control your blade.
Shut up!
Shut...
Stop hiding! Coward!
Do not let your emotions
overtake you.
Focus on the Force. Let it guide you.
Juro...
How did she...
All right. then...
She's reacting
faster than before.
Turning off your saber. huh?
If you think that's going to make it
harder for me to see you.
I'm afraid you're sorely mistaken.
When did she draw her weapon?
After the beam fired?
Did she just predict
where the beams will be coming from?
Is she reading Eht's mind?
No...
What is this?
Wait. Can she see them?
A silver lightsaber?
You...
Once I figured it out.
I knew it was another dirty trick.
You think this is a joke?
Never revealing
your finishing move...
That's a Jedi for you.
More blood. I have more blood on my hands.
This saber...
It's the same color as Nawaam's.
That means...
Were you fighting
without having any thoughts?
Yikes.
If I can't read your next move.
I can't risk closing the gap.
But... I can do this!
Do not play with me!
Aren't you gonna kill me?
If possible.
I'd rather not take any more lives.
Naive of me. huh?
Yeah. I'd say so.
Even so.
this means that from now on
your life belongs to me.
You will serve me
and follow the orders I give you.
Huh?
Understood?
All right. fine.
I guess I'll be calling you
Master from now on.
Were the two of you friends?
We worked together a long time.
He was a real piece of work.
But he treated his fellow hunters well.
You don't have to worry.
In this line of work.
trading lives is part of the game.
So. no hard feelings.
Here.
What's this?
You're gonna need it
if you're helping me.
Did I forget to mention.
you work for me now?
If you say so. But you better pay me well.
You said you liked fighting
strong enemies. didn't you?
Well. if you come with me.
then I promise.
you'll face a lot of strong enemies.
You mean Nawaam's army?
Well. that's a guaranteed death sentence.
Probably.
But you'll be able to fight
on the side of justice.
There we go. right on cue.
Again. with the Jedi teachings.
No. This has nothing to do
with rules or teachings.
It's something that must be done.
This is my decision.
Hmm.
You see? I knew I made the right choice.
Seriously?